<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lifestyle on TechDebtGyal</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/Lifestyle/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lifestyle on TechDebtGyal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2008–2018, Steve Francia and the Hugo Authors; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 04:30:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/Lifestyle/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> Expanding and Enhancing: Embracing Growth Beyond Your Comfort Zone in the Tech World</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/2023/08/expanding-and-enhancing-embracing.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 04:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/2023/08/expanding-and-enhancing-embracing.html</guid>
      <description>Entering the realm of technology is not for the faint-hearted or those who hold their egos above all else. This assertion is made with the utmost sincerity because in this dynamic domain, you&#39;ll find yourself confronted with more questions than certainties. Every day, as the sun rises, my mind is ablaze with inquiries - inquiries that pertain to unraveling a perplexing bug, diving into an unfamiliar framework at a client&#39;s request, or acquainting myself with a new programming language essential for a project&#39;s completion by week&#39;s end.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defying Conventions: Forging a Path in Software Engineering Without a Degree</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/2023/07/defying-conventions-forging-path-in.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 12:12:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/2023/07/defying-conventions-forging-path-in.html</guid>
      <description>This post speaks to those who have a drive for software engineering but do not have a degree in computer science or any associated area. Increasingly, more people are coming to the realization that programming can be learned independently, and a career can be attained by anyone with the diligence to figure it out, even without an academic background in the subject.&#xA;I had an interesting conversation with a group of peers on this topic recently.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlock the Secrets to Tech Blogging: A Call for YOU to Step Into The Limelight</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/2023/05/unlock-secrets-to-tech-blogging-call.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 06:10:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/2023/05/unlock-secrets-to-tech-blogging-call.html</guid>
      <description>I had been considering tech blogging for almost a year, wanting to expand my knowledge of programming and help others learn from my experiences. A few months ago, I finally decided it was time to take the plunge and commit to actively blogging.&#xA;This keeps me accountable, and when I document what I learn, new questions arise that inspire me to research further.&#xA;Working in tech thrusts you into a wild world of challenges and how you respond to them determines whether you&#39;re an average or proficient programmer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> It&#39;s Time to Take a Step Back...and That&#39;s OK</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/2023/04/its-time-to-take-step-backand-thats-ok.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 07:45:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/2023/04/its-time-to-take-step-backand-thats-ok.html</guid>
      <description>I am THE career woman. The hard worker. The one who always has ambition focused on providing for their family. I had the do-it-all attitude-- valuing independence and dedication to the point where I knew I could do anything if I put my heart into it. And this outlook resulted in great achievements and successes as well as an unbelievable amount of pressure.&#xA;I was the teammate unwilling to draw attention to myself, even if I handled the majority of the job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attention all Scrum Masters: Here&#39;s Why YOU Should Learn Programming!!! </title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/2023/04/attention-all-scrum-masters-heres-why.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 05:13:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/2023/04/attention-all-scrum-masters-heres-why.html</guid>
      <description>I find it concerning when people join online forums and discuss how to get a tech job without needing to ever touch code or have a degree in computer science, IT, or any other related field.&#xA;It only serves to make it tougher for those people who don&#39;t possess the diploma, but are serious about gaining experience, to be taken seriously. Eventually, businesses will start sifting through resumes and only consider applicants with relevant degrees from the industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five Reasons Why Applying for a Job in Tech May Not Be Right for You</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/2023/04/five-reasons-why-applying-for-job-in.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 06:41:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/2023/04/five-reasons-why-applying-for-job-in.html</guid>
      <description>At the beginning of my adulting journey, I had been searching for a way to make something of my life; a way to start a career and be able to travel the world at the same time. I&#39;ve heard of people doing it – making money online as digital nomads.&#xA;It seemed like something I could do, something that I could learn and make money from, in my own time and from anywhere in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Achieve Your Goals as a Woman in Tech: 10 Essential Questions to Ask Yourself for Success in the Industry.</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/2023/04/succeeding-as-woman-in-tech.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 16:47:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/2023/04/succeeding-as-woman-in-tech.html</guid>
      <description>The tech industry can be daunting, often evoking feelings of insecurity or questioning one&#39;s capacities. This is especially true for women and minorities who may experience even more alienation in this field due to any impolite remarks or animosity they may encounter in their surroundings.&#xA;I strive to maintain a sense of autonomy in my relationships with others, rather than attempt to manipulate their behavior. I focus on how I can manage my own thoughts and actions in response to those around me, rather than try to control their decisions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Simple Guide to Customizing Your Tech Workspace</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/2023/03/a-simple-guide-to-customizing-your-tech.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 05:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/2023/03/a-simple-guide-to-customizing-your-tech.html</guid>
      <description>Although some tech companies are pushing for workers to return to the office, many techies are embracing the work from home lifestyle. However, lifeless home offices can be dispiriting. Re-arranging and refreshing the atmosphere can help liven up the workspace. Why should we ignore our offices when we make time to decorate for holidays?&#xA;Your workspace should be where your creativity comes to life! When you step in the door, you should be ready to conquer, innovate, connect, and manage.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
